练习 4-6：规则三，阶梯底部。处在阶梯底部的 T
Exercise 4-6, Rule 3, Bottom of the Staircase. T at the bottom of a staircase
是 held 位置。所谓 held，我的意思是舌头在 T 的位置，但
is in the held position. By held, I mean that the tongue is in the T position, but
气流不释放。作个比较，当你说 Tom 里的 T 时，会有一股明显的气流
the air isn't released. To compare, when you say T as in Tom, there's a sharp burst
从舌尖上方爆出；当你说 Betty 时，则是一股柔和的
of air over the tip of the tongue, and when you say Betty, there's a soft puff of
而 hold 住 T 时，舌头仍在 T 的位置，
air over the tip of the tongue. When you hold a T, as in hot, your T is in the
position for T, but you keep the air in. 1. She hit the hot hut with her hat. 2. We
went to that net site to get what we needed. 3. Pat was quite right, wasn't
she? 4. What? Put my hat back. Five. Hot. Late. Fat. Goat. Hit. Put. Knot. Hurt.
What. Set. Paint. Weight. Sit. Dirt. Note. Fit. Lot. Light. Suit. Point. Incident.
Tight.